hello everyone last Friday April 26th my
family received news that emergency
surgical intervention
the second in a two-month period was
necessary for my wife Tammy we and many
other family members and friends have
spent the last week conferring with
specialists in multiple hospitals in
multiple cities confirming the diagnosis
and specifying the proper course of
action there are still test results
pending but the procedure is currently
and suddenly scheduled for May 9th
thus it is impossible for me to maintain
my obligations regarding my scheduled
talks at the Polish National Foundation
100 times 100 event in Poznan Poland on
Tuesday May 7th or at the Apollo Theater
in London England
on may 8th I am truly sorry for the
inconvenience that this has caused for
all those who planned and purchased and
arranged travel to attend these lectures
we are truly grateful for all the
support and good wishes we have received
during this period and would very much
like to thank those who have done what
they could to make the last week as
bearable as possible we are hoping and
praying that things go well and that we
are fortunate enough so that recovery
remains an option thank you all for your
understanding and continued support
bye-bye